Gloria Delgado

UX/UI Designer

ABOUT ME

UX/UI Designer with solid experience in web design and digital marketing, combining user experience with business objectives. I work closely with multidisciplinary teams, ensuring the creation of functional and user-friendly interfaces, using data insights to achieve the best results.

EXPERIENCE

UX/UI Designer & WordPress Web Design Specialist

Consejo Superior De Investigaciones Científicas (CSIC) / Madrid

- Collecting and incorporating qualitative and quantitative data in order to iterate and improve the overall user experience.
- Connecting the needs of the organization with development, translating stakeholder requirements and user feedback into user-centered web solutions, including CMS platforms.
- Ideating wireframes and prototypes in Figma, ensuring alignment with technical constraints and seamless communication with stakeholders.
- Actively collaborating with the development team to ensure the implementation of the validated user-centered solution by customizing CMS platforms.

UX/UI Designer & Content Strategist

Parada Creativa / Granada

- Executed web design with a strong focus on aligning user preferences with business objectives.
- Designed Search Engine Marketing (SEM) and email marketing campaigns, leveraging expertise in usability to enhance effectiveness.
- Implemented UX copywriting and Search Engine Optimization (SEO), bringing a wealth of experience in enhancing user navigation, accessibility, and search visibility.

December 2020 -Current

May 2018 -June 2019



Digital Marketing & UX Specialist

GES Formación / Granada

October 2017

- May 2018
- Created engaging visual content and managed social media, focusing on maximizing user interaction and engagement.
- Designed email marketing templates, leveraging expertise in usability to drive user-friendly experiences.
- Optimized Search Engine Optimization (SEO) strategies, enhancing user experience and improving accessibility.

EDUCATION -

January 2024 - Current

Master in UX/UI and Web Development

CEI - Centro de Estudios de Innovación / Madrid

Specialized in UX/UI design, focused on crafting user-centered designs, complemented by knowledge in front-end development.

2017 - 2020

Master in Digital Marketing and Social Media

Universidad a Distancia de Madrid

Specialized in digital marketing strategy, SEO/SEM, social media management, and data-driven optimization.

2012 - 2016

Bachelor's Degree in Advertising and **Public Relations**

Universidad Complutense de Madrid

SKILLS

- Recognize Business Needs
- Design Thinking Methodology
- User Research & Data Analysis
- Personas & User Journey Maps
- Information Architecture and Sitemap
- Wireframing & Prototyping
- Design Systems & Style Guides
- Web & Responsive Design
- Usability Testing
- Collaborative Mindset
- Problem Solving & Autonomy
- Communication and Work Facilitation
- Empathy
- Adaptability

TOOLS -

Design tools:

Figma Photoshop Whimsical

Research tools:

Google Analytics Maze

Additional tools:

WordPress Drupal HTML CSS JavaScript